<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="108">
    <author>KeilerHirsch</author>
    <version>0.2.1.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Iron Horse Realism</en>
        <de>Iron Horse Realism</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Iron Horse Realism is an original, from-scratch vehicle realism framework for Farming Simulator 25. It unifies engine health, drivetrain, tire pressure, electrical, dirt/visuals and a field-repair toolbox into ONE coherent drivetrain chain with ONE HUD.

Foundation release (0.1.x): modular core only. Features are added as self-contained modules.

This mod REPLACES separate wear / drive-assist / tire-pressure mods and takes technical precedence over them when present. Values are grounded in real manufacturer data. Designed for dedicated-server multiplayer.]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Iron Horse Realism ist ein eigenstaendiges, von Grund auf geschriebenes Fahrzeug-Realismus-Framework fuer Farming Simulator 25. Es vereint Motorzustand, Antriebsstrang, Reifendruck, Elektrik, Schmutz/Optik und einen Behelfsreparatur-Werkzeugkasten zu EINER kohaerenten Antriebsstrang-Kette mit EINEM HUD.

Fundament-Release (0.1.x): nur der modulare Kern. Features kommen als eigenstaendige Module dazu.

Dieser Mod ERSETZT separate Verschleiss-/Fahrhilfe-/Reifendruck-Mods und hat technischen Vorrang vor ihnen, wenn sie geladen sind. Werte beruhen auf realen Herstellerdaten. Fuer Dedicated-Server-Mehrspieler ausgelegt.]]></de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_ironHorseRealism.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/IronHorseRealism.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <actions>
        <action name="IH_FIELD_REPAIR"/>
    </actions>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="IH_FIELD_REPAIR">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_r"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
    <l10n>
        <text name="input_IH_FIELD_REPAIR">
            <en>Field repair (IronHorse)</en>
            <de>Feldreparatur (IronHorse)</de>
        </text>
    </l10n>
</modDesc>
